







Summary

Jump to Section

5 years of total IT Industry Experience in Ticket Handling, Document Management, Asset Inventory Management, SAP, SLA Report generation, Resource Management, Project code Creation (WBS Creation, Role mapping)Quality Analyst, Governance Boards, Working with Reputed Pharma Project Novartis and British Telecom.

Experience includes working on Profit Improvement Plan.

Experience in resource Management, Operations and Logistic Management

Good Knowledge about Compliance activities, Distribution List Management

Strong foundation in CAPEX and Invoicing Management

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Capable of learning new technologies and tools quickly

Ability to work & gel in team oriented projects.

Work Experience

Tata Consultancy Services as Assistant Manager Dec 2019 to Mar 2020

Software and hardware asset management Service now Ticket management AVDB management

- HCL Tech as Assistant Manager Jun 2013 to Till Date
- Wipro Limited as System Engineer May 2012 to Oct 2012

Working on internal tool, handling tickets query.

^ Back to Top

Education

 $\hbox{UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Maharishi Dayanand University (MDU), Rohtak in 2012}\\$

PG: Other (Other) in 0

Important

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used	Experience
C, C++ programming languages		
MS Office, SAP		
MS Project		
Hardware Asset management	0	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

^ Back to Top

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Expert	✓	✓	✓

^ Back to Top

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources
Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICICIcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India
All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.